Hello everyone. In this video, I want to show you something
大家好。在这个视频里，我想向大家展示一个
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
使用AI工具翻译，如有不准确的地方请在弹幕或评论区指正，谢谢！
翻译质量权威评价：原来25年就有小拉即用机翻糊弄人了
cool you can do with Since most a Chromiumbas based browser.
很酷的功能，这个功能可以在大多数基于Chromium的浏览器中实现
browsers are just Chrome derivatives, I think it's
浏览器不过是Chrome的衍生品罢了，我觉得
it's going to work on like 90% of the browsers out there.
它能在市面上90%的浏览器上运行
And you can impress your friends with this
你可以用这个或类似的东西给你的朋友留下深刻印象
or something. So, here is the thing. You can
所以，事情是这样的
if you're using Edge, using Chrome
如果你用的是Edge、Chrome
or any other Chrome derivative really, you can just
或任何其他基于Chrome的浏览器，你完全可以输入这个URL
(/▽＼)不要盯着人家惠惠(Megumin)啦~ 好好看视频操作 (✿◡‿◡)
Hit enter
猛按回车键
and your browser crashes.
然后浏览器崩溃了耶~~~
it no longer works. I mean, you have to you have to close it.
现在它动不了了，只能强制关闭
There you go. Once you reopen it, it's it's going to be good. It's going to be fine.
就是这样。 再次打开它，一切都好起来了
But yeah, that's a thing.
就是这样
there are a couple more flags that sound hip
还有几个听起来
that sound gangster, you can look them up here.
很潮、很野的标志
And you have a list of something URLs depends on the fork.
根据不同的分支，你会有一个包含某些URL的列表
since Edge is a Chromium fork, they just edited the strings.
由于Edge是Chromium的一个分支，他们只是修改了字符串
And at the very end right here,
而在最后这里
you see um for debug category.
你会看到调试分类
here is all the stuff you can
以下是你可以
insert into the address bar and
输入地址栏的所有内容
basically just enjoy enjoy the show.
基本上就是享受这场表演
it's been here for a while. I guess it's been here for years
它已经存在一段时间了。我猜它已经存在好几年了
and, I was really surprised to learn that
而且，我真的很惊讶地发现
not a lot of people knew about this and just kind of blew up on Twitter
没有多少人知道这件事，只是在推特上突然火了起来
and people were like,
人们都惊了
"What? What the heck? This actually worked.
“啥？搞什么鬼？这居然真能行
No way. This actually crashed my browser."
不可能吧。这真的把我的浏览器搞崩了。”
So yeah, I just wanted to make a quick video
所以呢，我就想快速做个视频强调一下
原标题：The Coolest Way to Crash a Browser 原作者：Enderman
原视频上传日期：2025年4月29日
to highlight you can induce the browser crash for reals on any Chromium derivative.
你确实能在任何基于Chromium的浏览器上人为引发崩溃
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
翻译质量权威评价：原来25年就有小拉即用机翻糊弄人了
yeah, have fun with this. Impress your friends.
好的，玩得开心。让你的朋友们留下深刻印象 o(￣ヘ￣o＃)
Thanks for watching. Take care.
感谢观看。保重